truglamour.com 2019-03-19

# Privacy Policy - TruGlamour

Effective Date: March 2016

Before using the TruGlamour.com & TruGlamour-news.com (“we”, “us” or “our”) website, please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy provides an explanation of what information we collect, how we collect it, how we use it and disclose it, and what choices you have regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of your information. By using any part of our website you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as described herein.

### Applicability and Third Party Websites and Services

This Privacy Policy only applies to our website and does not apply to third party websites you may reach by clicking a link, advertisement or other online material located on this Site, or third-party websites or other online services which may be displayed on this Site. If you click on a link to a third party website or other online service, or supply information to a third party website or other online service that is placed within our webpage, you are interacting with that third party and this Privacy Policy will not apply. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third party websites and services.

### We may collect your personal information in the following ways:

  1. When you sign up to receive our newsletter, when you register with our site to complete quizzes and surveys, or when you otherwise provide us with your information;

  2. From third parties, including websites which publish our ads and offers, as well as other online and offline sources such as identity verification services, and other service providers and vendors, and we may combine such information with other information you have provided to us; and

  3. Automatically based on interaction with our site with the use of cookies and other technology (as described below).

### Information We May Collect

Personally identifying information you provide:

Examples of the types of personally identifying the information you may provide include, but are not limited to, your name, email address, telephone number, age, birthday, zip code, payment card information, optional profile photo, your interests in and use of various products and services and other information.

Other information we collect:

We automatically collect information about your interaction with our Site, our advertisements and other promotional content using technologies like cookies and web beacons, and via our web server’s log files. Examples of information which may be collected by our various technologies include browser information, your device IP address, whether you clicked on one of our advertisements, pages you’ve visited on the Site, which website you came from, date and time stamp information, and other navigation and click-through information. Although the information we collect through these tracking devices is not always personally identifying when collected, we may combine such information with personally identifying information like your name or email address or other information that could be used to identify you.

### How we use your information

The information that we collect about you may be used by us and shared by us with third parties in any manner and for any purpose permitted by law. This may include disclosing (with or without remuneration) the personally identifying information that we collect to third parties for their marketing purposes. Once we provide your information to a third party for any reason, we do not control and are not responsible for that third party’s use or disclosure of such information. Examples of the ways we may use the information and with whom we may share the information that we collect include:

  * With third parties in connection with processing or fulfilling your requests or inquiries;

  * With companies who may use such information for their own marketing purposes, including to contact you in order to offer you their products or services or the products or services of other third parties;

  * With companies who may resell, exchange or otherwise provide your information to other businesses for various marketing purposes, including to contact you with offers regarding third party products or services;

  * With advertisers whose content we publish or display, their agents, third party ad servers, and service providers;

  * With service providers we engage to provide us with services that support our business;

  * In response to government or regulatory agency requests, court orders, subpoenas, or as we otherwise believe to be required or permitted in connection with any applicable law, rule or regulation;

  * As we believe necessary or desirable to protect our business, rights, safety, assets, or property, or those of a third party; to limit our legal liability; to defend our interests or the interests of you or a third party, or to enforce our Terms of Service or other rules; and

  * In connection with the consolidation or sale of or other transactions related to our business.

### How You Can Opt-Out of Certain Data Sharing

Any personal information collected may be shared immediately for direct marketing purposes, but you may opt-out of further sharing for direct marketing by submitting your request newstruglamour@gmail.com

### Cookies and Other Technology

Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer or device by your web browser. We use cookies to store information so that you do not have to re-enter your information upon revisiting one of our Sites. Cookies also enable us to provide personalized content, monitor our marketing campaigns, track your entries and submissions and gather information about your interactions with our Site or with one of our advertisements. Cookies may be set by us or our business partners and service providers when you visit the Site or when you interact with one of our advertisements or other content. We use both session cookies, which terminate when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which may remain on your computer until you delete them. You may decline cookies if your web browser software permits. If you have questions about disabling cookies, you should consult with your browser’s manufacturer. Note, however, that some parts of the Site may not operate correctly if you disable cookies.We may also track your use of our Site, advertisements and other content through web beacons (also called pixel tags or clear gifs). Web beacons can be used for various purposes, including helping us improve our Site, services and marketing communications.

### Blogs and Public Forums

TruGlamour features blogs and public forums where users may discuss certain beauty topics and share their stories with other members within the community. In order to participate in the conversations and post comments on our blogs and public forums you must register for membership but conversations and comments are viewable to the public and should not be considered private.Any information you share on our blogs and public forums (including personally identifying information or personal medical information) is open to the public and not private. You should think carefully before posting any personally identifying information. What you post can be seen, disclosed to or collected by third parties and may be used by others in ways we cannot control or predict, including to contact you for unauthorized purposes. Such posted information may also appear in search engine results generated by Yahoo, Google, Bing, MSN, and other search engines. TruGlamour reserves the rights to remove any verbiage on our blogs and public forums that we deem inappropriate.

### Targeted Ads and Analytics Services

We have relationships with third-party advertising and analytics service companies who may place a cookie on your computer or device when you visit our site or use web beacons for the purpose of collecting information which may include, but is not limited to, information about the websites you view and advertisements you interact with, your IP address, date/time stamp information, your ISP and the browser you use to visit this Site. Any information collected may be may be linked to information provided by other third parties and may be used for, among other things, to deliver advertising (from us and from other companies) targeted to your preferences and interests, and to better understand the usage and visitation of our Site and the other websites tracked by these advertising companies. In addition, this information may be shared by such third party advertising and analytical service companies with other third parties for the purpose of targeting advertisements to your preferences and interests. Such third parties may also place advertisements on our behalf onto other websites, perform tracking and reporting functions for those sites and our advertisements, and place third party advertisements on our Site. To learn more about targeted advertising (also called behavioral advertising), analytics services and your choices, including how to opt-out of targeted advertising, you may visit the NAI Consumer Opt-Out Page and the Google information page.

### Your choices regarding the collection of your information.

Providing Information.

You can choose not to provide us with your personally identifying information. Note, however, that you may not have access to certain of our products and services if you decide not to provide us with your information.

Opting Out of Our Promotional Emails

You may opt-out of receiving marketing and promotional emails from us at any time by using the opt-out mechanism contained in such emails (also referred to as “unsubscribe”), or by submitting your request to newstruglamour@gmail.com. Please allow 10 business days for us to process your opt-out request. Also, note that opting out of receiving promotional email communications will affect only future communications from us. If we already provided your information to a third party before you changed your preferences or updated your information, you may have to change your preferences directly with that third party as well.

Declining Cookies

If you do not want to accept our cookies, you can adjust your browser settings to decline cookies. You should note, however, that certain areas of the Site may not operate properly if you decide not to accept cookies.

Behavioral Advertising Opt-Out

Some third-party advertising companies may collect information about you through cookies and other technologies in connection with their behavioral advertising programs. For information on opting out from behavioral advertising practices, please refer to the Targeted Ads and Analytics Services section above.

### Children’s Privacy

This Site is intended for general audiences and is not intended for use by persons under the age of 13. If we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete it. If you believe that we have collected personal information from a child under 13, please contact us using the information below.

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting an updated Privacy Policy to our Site without advance notice to you. We encourage you to check this page often for updates and revisions. Any updated Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments relating to our website, this notice, or would like to access or correct the information we may hold about you, please contact us by email at: newstruglamour@gmail.com You may also send your questions or comments to our address: TruGlamour P.O Box Little Ferry, NJ 07643 Phone: (coming soon)
